Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Israeli Elections with Molly Malekar; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-053], 1999 May 30; 1999 June 6; cuid33990 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0225)
  Duration: 1:57:39, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0238, 718_0452, 718_0465
- A: Israeli Elections with Molly Malekar; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur / B: INS Detainee, Lulseged Dhine; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-066], 1999 May 30; 1999 June 6; cuid33991 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0238)
  Duration: 1:57:21, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0225, 718_0452, 718_0465
- INS Detainee, Lulseged Dhine; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-038], 1999-05-30; cuid33992 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0452)
  Duration: 0:58:56, Preservation Note: Digital Dropouts During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0225, 718_0238, 718_0465
- Israeli Elections; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur [1999-018], 1999-06-06; cuid33993 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0465)
  Duration: 0:55:41, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0225, 718_0238, 718_0452
- Police in Schools Forum [1999-052], 1999-06-13; cuid33994 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0224)
  Duration: 0:54:59, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; No Left Channel Until 00:10:07 on Side A During Program
- Police in Schools Forum with Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley; Schmidt Report on CUNY; Community Gardens Mark Leger and Tom Goodridge [1999-014], 1999-06-13; cuid33995 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0461)
  Duration: 0:31:02, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Digital Dropouts During Program; Program Distorted at Times; First Segment of Program Unplayable
  Duplicate of 718_0262, 718_0262
- Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two; Ethnic Parades and Gay Inclusion [1999-051], 1999 June 20; 1999 June 27; cuid33996 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0223)
  Duration: 1:54:21, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0255, 718_0462, 718_0463
- A: Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two / B: Ethnic Parades and Gay Inclusion; Joan Nestle on Fragile Union [1999-084], 1999 June 20; 1999 June 27; cuid33997 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0255)
  Duration: 1:54:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0223, 718_0462, 718_0463
- Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two (Partial) [1999-015], 1999-06-20; cuid33998 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0462)
  Duration: 0:48:19
  Duplicate of 718_0223, 718_0255, 718_0463
- Ethnic Parades (Puerto Rican Day Parade, St. Patrick's Day Parade, Israel Day Parade); Joan Nestle on Fragile Union [1999-016], 1999-06-27; cuid33999 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0463)
  Duration: 0:55:12, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Digital Dropouts During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0223, 718_0255, 718_0462
- A: Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving; Marcia Falk Reading / B: David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-058], 1999 July 4; 1999 September 19; cuid34000 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0230)
  Duration: 1:00:16, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hiss During Program; Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0256, 718_0466, 718_0451, 718_0940
- A: Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving; Marcia Falk Reading; Lorin Sklamberg with Music for High Holy Days / B: David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Zalmen Mlotek on Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-083], 1999 July 4; 1999 September 19; cuid34001 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0256)
  Duration: 1:00:41, Preservation Note: Speed Fluctuations at End; Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0230, 718_0466, 718_0451, 718_0940
- David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Zalmen Mlotek on Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-019], 1999-07-04; cuid34002 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0466)
  Duration: 1:00:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0230, 718_0256, 718_0451, 718_0940
- Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses; Yemenite Music with Lorin Sklamberg; Food Shopping with Myra Alperson [1999-056], 1999 July 11; 1999 September 12; cuid34003 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0228)
  Duration: 0:59:06, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0253, 718_0428
- A: Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses / B: Food Shopping with Myra Alperson; E.M. Bronner on Bringing Home the Light [1999-082], 1999 July 11; 1999 September 12; cuid34004 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0253)
  Duration: 1:00:22, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0228, 718_0428
- Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses; Yemenite Music with Lorin Sklamberg [1999-007], 1999-07-11; cuid34005 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0428)
  Duration: 0:59:31, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0228, 718_0253
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading; Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis [1999-055], 1999 July 18; 1999 August 8; cuid34006 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0227)
  Duration: 1:31:36, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0254, 718_0458, 718_0450
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading / B: Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis (Partial) [1999-081], 1999 July 18; 1999 August 8; cuid34007 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0254)
  Duration: 1:32:24, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0227, 718_0458, 718_0450
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading [1999-044], 1999-07-18; cuid34008 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0458)
  Duration: 0:58:08, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During End of Program
  Duplicate of 718_0227, 718_0254, 718_0450
- Adrienne Rich Reading [1997-023], 1999-07-25; cuid34009 (Box 24, Reel 718_0998)
  Duration: 0:56:10, Preservation Note: Broken Splices Repaired; Program Distorted at Times
- Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign [1999-068], 1999 August 1; 1999 August 15; cuid34010 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0240)
  Duration: 1:01:19, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0252, 718_0436
- A: Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Jim Ledbetter on Public Broadcast; Call-ins about Community Radio and Pacifica / B: Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign; Rebroadcast of 1998 Interview with Dr. Tal Jarus-Hakak (Partial) [1999-080], 1999 August 1; 1999 August 15; cuid34011 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0252)
  Duration: 1:01:44, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank; Speed Fluctuations During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0240, 718_0436
- Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign; Rebroadcast of 1998 Interview with Dr. Tal Jarus-Hakak (Partial) [1999-010], 1999-08-01; cuid34012 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0431)
- Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis (Partial); Cindy Greenberg and Gail Zoffer of Minneapolis Jewish Community Action [1999-036], 1999-08-08; cuid34013 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0450)
  Duration: 0:36:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0227, 718_0254, 718_0458
- Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Jim Ledbetter on Public Broadcast; Call-ins about Community Radio and Pacifica [1999-022], 1999-08-15; cuid34014 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0436)
  Duration: 1:01:20, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0240, 718_0252
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-069], 1999 August 22; cuid34015 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0241)
  Duration: 0:53:38, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0251, 718_0437
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-079], 1999-08-22; cuid34016 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0251)
  Duration: 0:50:47, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0241, 718_0437
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-023], 1999-08-22; cuid34017 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0437)
  Duration: 0:50:02
  Duplicate of 718_0241, 718_0251
- A: Riverdale School Board Controversy / B: Kansas Anti-Evolution Curriculum [1999-071], 1999 August 29; 1999 November 21; cuid34018 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0243)
  Duration: 0:57:28, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0250, 718_0438, 718_0430
- A: Riverdale School Controversy with Oliver Koppell and Charles Williams; Blanche Wiesen Cook on Eleanor Roosevelt, Vol. 2 / B: Kansas Anti-Evolution Curriculum; Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley, Naomi Mezey, and Eric Zinner on Circumcision [1999-078], 1999 August 29; 1999 November 21; cuid34019 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0250)
  Duration: 0:57:37, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0243, 718_0438, 718_0430
- Kansas Anti-Evolution State Standards; Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley, Naomi Mezey, and Eric Zinner on Circumcision [1999-024], 1999-08-29; cuid34020 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0438)
  Duration: 0:59:55, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0243, 718_0250, 718_0430
- Rosh Hashanah: Food Shopping with Myra Alperson; E.M. Bronner on Bringing Home the Light [1999-025], 1999-09-12; cuid34021 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0439)
  Duration: 0:58:19, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving (Ethics); Marcia Falk Reading (Prayer); Lorin Sklamberg with Music for High Holy Days (Music) [1999-037], 1999-09-19; cuid34022 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0451)
  Duration: 0:59:36
  Duplicate of 718_0230, 718_0256, 718_0466, 718_0940
- Randy Cohen [1999-002], 1999-09-19; cuid34023 (Box 21, Reel 718_0940)
  Duration: 0:15:48
  Duplicate of 718_0230, 718_0256, 718_0451, 718_0466
- Trafficking and the Sex Trade; Lisa Schiffman on Generation J.; David Lang and Ben Katchor on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-033], 1999 September 26; 1999 October 3; cuid34024 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0237)
  Duration: 1:16:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0321, 718_0232, 718_0447, 718_0449
- Campaign for Fiscal Equity Lawsuit; Palestinian Youth Dance Troupe; Trafficking Women [1999-035], 1999-09-26; cuid34025 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0449)
  Duration: 0:57:43
  Duplicate of 718_0231, 718_0232, 718_0237, 718_0447
- Tom Segev on Israeli Elections [1999-085], 1999-10-01; cuid34026 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0257)
  Duration: 0:55:56, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
- Aaron Taub Interviews Lisa Schiffman on Generation J. and David Lang on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-059], 1999-10-03; cuid34027 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0231)
  Duration: 0:56:50, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0232, 718_0237, 718_0447, 718_0449
- Aaron Taub Interviews Lisa Schiffman on Generation J. and David Lang on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-060], 1999-10-03; cuid34028 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0232)
  Duration: 0:57:34, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0231, 718_0237, 718_0447, 718_0449
- Lisa Schiffman on Generation J.; David Lang and Ben Katchor on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-033], 1999-10-03; cuid34029 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0447)
  Duration: 0:56:19, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0231, 718_0232, 718_0237, 718_0449
- Emma Lazarus Marathon: Mike Wishnie, Shirley Romaine, New Colossus Voices, Hour 3 [1999-077], 1999-10-10; cuid34030 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0249)
  Duration: 0:55:14, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0242
- 2 Hour Special on Emma Lazarus, 1999-10-17; cuid34031 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0239)
  Duration: 1:47:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Dropout at Start of Side A During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0440, 718_0441
- Marathon Show: Mike Wishnie, Shirley Romaine [1999-070], 1999-10-17; cuid34032 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0242)
  Duration: 0:55:21, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0249, 718_0442
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 1 [1999-026], 1999-10-17; cuid34033 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0440)
  Duplicate of 718_0239
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 2 [1999-027], 1999-10-17; cuid34034 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0441)
  Duration: 0:53:02
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 3 [1999-028], 1999-10-17; cuid34035 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0442)
  Duration: 0:49:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0242, 718_0249
- Emma Lazarus Marathon: The Statue of Liberty - Its Meaning [1999-001], 1999-10-17; cuid34036 (Box 21, Reel 718_0939)
  Duration: 0:06:17, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0239, 718_0242, 718_0249, 718_0440, 718_0441, 718_0442
- A: Update on Israel/Palestine with Gila Svirsky and Gershon Baskin; Marshall Meyer Awarding Honoring the CUNY Struggle / B: Allegra Pacheco on Israeli Supreme Court Decision on Torture; Karen Brodkin on Jews and Whiteness [1999-076], 1999 October 31; 1999 November 7; cuid34037 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0248)
  Duration: 0:59:21, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0454
- Update on Israel/Palestine with Gila Svirsky and Gershon Baskin; Marshall Meyer Awarding Honoring the CUNY Struggle; Andy Stettner and Dillona Lewis; Abraham Polansky [1999-040], 1999-10-31; cuid34038 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0454)
  Duration: 0:59:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0248
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville Dub, Part 1 [1999-006], 1999-11-11; cuid34039 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0427)
  Duration: 1:01:37, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0152, 718_0199, 718_0414, 718_0415, 718_0263
- Jeremy Burton on Hillary Clinton; Glen Busch, Iris Baez, and Richie Perez on Police Brutality Cases; Alicia Svigals and Elizabeth Ziff on Jewish Women, Lesbians, and Music [1999-074], 1999-11-14; cuid34040 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0246)
  Duration: 0:42:13, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0459
- Jeremy Burton on Hillary Clinton; Glen Busch, Iris Baez, and Richie Perez on Police Brutality Cases; Alicia Svigals and Elizabeth Ziff on Jewish Women, Lesbians, and Music (Partial Show) [1999-092], 1999-11-14; cuid34041 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0459)
  Duration: 0:33:12, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0246
- Charles Williams and Oliver Koppell on District 10 County School Board; Blanche Wiesen Cook on Eleanor Roosevelt, Vol. 2 [1999-009], 1999-11-21; cuid34042 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0430)
  Duration: 0:58:54
  Duplicate of 718_0243, 718_0250, 718_0438
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Alisse Waterston on Love, Sorrow, and Rage; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown; Jim Hoberman on the Russian Film Festival; Gil Marks on Book The World of Jewish Cooking; David Gitlitz and Linda Davidson on Book A Drizzle of Honey; Jordan Elgrably Interview [1999-064], 1999 November 28; 1999 December 5; cuid34043 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0236)
  Duration: 1:59:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0245, 718_0429
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown [1999-073], 1999 November 28; cuid34044 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0245)
  Duration: 0:59:55, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0236, 718_0429
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Alisse Waterston on Love, Sorrow, and Rage; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown [1999-008], 1999-11-28; cuid34045 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0429)
  Duration: 0:59:53
  Duplicate of 718_0236, 718_0245
- Hanukkah Show with Jim Hoberman on the Russian Film Festival; Gil Marks on Book The World of Jewish Cooking [1999-062], 1999-12-05; cuid34046 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0234)
  Duration: 0:58:08, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0443
- Hanukkah Show [1999-029], 1999-12-05; cuid34047 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0443)
  Duration: 0:58:04
  Duplicate of 718_0234
- A: Jack Foner Obituary; Hidden Jews of New Mexico, Parts 2 and 3 / B: Mark and Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson's Incarceration; Kathryn Hellerstein on Katya Molodovsky [1999-061], 1999 December 12; 1999 December 19; cuid34048 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0233)
  Duration: 1:58:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0235, 718_0424, 718_0453
- Parts 2 and 3 Hidden Jews of New Mexico; On Lori Berenson's Incarceration [1999-063], 1999 December 12; 1999 December 19; cuid34049 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0235)
  Duration: 2:00:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0233, 718_0424
- Mark and Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson; Kathryn Hellerstein on Katya Molodovsky [1999-039], 1999-12-12; cuid34050 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0453)
  Duration: 0:59:41, Preservation Note: Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0233
- Jack Foner Obituary; Hidden Jews of New Mexico, Parts 2 and 3, 1999-12-19; cuid34051 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0424)
  Duration: 0:57:03, Preservation Note: Channel Imbalance at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0233, 718_0235
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Parts 1 and 2 [1999-057], 1999-12-26; cuid34052 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0229)
  Duration: 1:58:32, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0432, 718_0433
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 1 [1999-011], 1999-12-26; cuid34053 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0432)
  Duration: 1:07:05, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Rebroadcast of original episode; Related to 718_0152, 718_0199, 718_0414, 718_0415, 718_0263, 718_0427
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 1 (cont'd) and Part 2 [1999-012], 1999-12-26; cuid34054 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0433)
  Duration: 0:49:02, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Jafar (Continued); Ronen Wolf of Ta'ayush; Amal Alnasasra, Bedouin Activist; Soosia Area of 10F Destruction; Meeting in Yatta to Plan Convoy [2015-019], circa 2000-2013 (Box 20, Item 718_1017)
- Summer Nights '00 at the Jewish Museum [2000-048], Summer 2000; cuid34055 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0484)
  Duration: 0:05:41
- Meeting in Yatta (Track 1) - Tracks Recorded in Israel/Palestine During Second Intifada [2015-020], circa 2000-2005 (Box 20, Item 718_1014)
- Diallo Protest [2000-090-z], cuid34056 (Box 21, Audiocassette 718_0944)
  Duration: 0:05:55, Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Palestinian and Israeli Women's Peace Activism with Gila Svirsky and Isla Hajad [2015-003], circa 2000-2007; cuid34057 (Box 23, Reel 718_0992)
  Duration: 0:29:33, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- A: Millennium Show / B: Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial [2000-009], 2000 January 2; 2000 February 13; cuid34058 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0272)
  Duration: 1:57:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0277, 718_0506, 718_0503
- A: Millennium Show / B: Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial; Larry Cohler-Esses on Daycare Voucher Scandal; Melvin Jules Bukiet on Neurotica [2000-14], 2000 February 13; 2000 January 2; cuid34059 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0277)
  Duplicate of 718_0272, 718_0506, 718_0503
- Millenium Show [2000-070], 2000-01-02; cuid34060 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0506)
  Duration: 0:56:24
  Duplicate of 718_0272, 718_0277
- A: Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena / B: Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln" [2000-005], 2000 January 9; 2000 January 30; cuid34061 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0268)
  Duration: 2:00:16, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0284, 718_0481, 718_0475
- A: Aviva Kempner on The Life and Times of Hank Greenberg Film; Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena / B: Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln"; Shelley Hirsch on "My Father Piece"; Andy Ingall and Stacy Woolf on "Viva La Diva: Jewish Superstars of Song" Lecture [2000-21], 2000 January 9; 2000 January 30; cuid34062 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0284)
  Duration: 2:02:01, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0268, 718_0481, 718_0475
- Aviva Kempner on The Life and Times of Hank Greenberg Film; Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena [2000-045], 2000-01-09; cuid34063 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0481)
  Duration: 0:59:10, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0268, 718_0284
- Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln"; Shelley Hirsch on "My Father Piece"; Andy Ingall and Stacy Woolf on "Viva La Diva: Jewish Superstars of Song" Lecture [2000-039], 2000-01-30; cuid34064 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0475)
  Duration: 0:59:13, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
- A: Rabbis' Letter on Jerusalem; Michel Warschawski on Lebanon Bombing / B: Discussion of Jörg Haider [2000-15], 2000 February 6; 2000 February 20; cuid34065 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0278)
  Duration: 1:51:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0279, 718_0490
- A: Jerome Siegel on 100 Rabbis' Letter; Michel Warschawski on Lebanon Bombing; Megan Ortiz with Updates on Diallo Trial; David Espar on Lost Tribes of Israel / B: Discussion of Jörg Haider (Partial); Andy Statman on Mountain Jewish Music; Avi Shlaim on Israel and Arabs [2000-16], 2000 February 6; 2000 February 20; cuid34066 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0279)
  Duration: 1:51:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0278, 718_0490
- Michael Alpert on Jewish Mountain Music of the Caucasus; Avi Shlaim on Iron Wall (Partial) [2000-054], 2000-02-06; cuid34067 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0490)
  Duration: 0:49:44, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0278, 718_0279
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial; Larry Cohler-Esses on Daycare Voucher Scandal; Melvin Jules Bukiet on Neurotica [2000-067], 2000-02-13; cuid34068 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0503)
  Duration: 1:03:23, Preservation Note: Digital Errors and Dropouts During Program; Program in Silence from 04:28 to 26:07, 26:59 to 27:58, and from 32:53 to 36:05; Clicks and Pops During Program
- Jerome Siegel on Rabbis' Letter; Michel Warschawski on Jerusalem; Megan Ortiz on Diallo Trial; David Espar on Lost Tribes of Israel [2000-068], 2000-02-20; cuid34069 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0504)